<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
	<name>RimThreaded [1.2]</name>
	<author>Major Hoff</author>
	<packageId>majorhoff.rimthreaded</packageId>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.2</li>
	</supportedVersions>
  <description>
    RimThreaded enables Rimworld to utilize multiple threads and thus greatly increases the speed of the game.

    Version 1.0.21
    -Fixed bug with AmbientSoundManager
    -Fixed bug with Pawn_PathFollower
    -Fixed bug with Region
    -Fixed bug with ReservationManager
    -Fixed bug with SustainerManager
    -Fixed bug with ThingGrid (Building_Door)

    DESCRIPTION:
    This project is still a work in progress and will likely not play well with other mods. I am uploading this hoping to get feedback and identify some bugs as I continue development. If you would like to contribute, I have provided a github link below. Submissions of bug reports with error logs are the most helpful to progress this project! Also submitting lists of known working and incompatible mods helps too.

    NOTE: The number of threads to utilize should be set in the mod settings, according to your specific computer's core count.

    LOAD ORDER:
    After: Core, Royalty, and Harmony
    Before: Everything else, most likely

    BUGS:
    https://github.com/cseelhoff/RimThreaded/issues
    Your (likely) log location: C:\Users\username\AppData\LocalLow\Ludeon Studios\RimWorld by Ludeon Studios\player.log

    CREDITS:

    Bug testing:
    Special thank you for helping me test Austin (Stanui)!
    And thank you to others in Rimworld community who have posted their bug findings!

    Coding:
    Big thanks to Kiame Vivacity for all of his help! including fixing the sound issue that was driving me nuts!
    Thank you to Ataman for helping me fix the LVM deep storage bug

    Logo:
    Thank you ArchieV1 for the logo! (https://github.com/ArchieV1)
    Logo help from: Marnador (https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?action=profile;u=36313) and JKimsey (https://pixabay.com/users/jkimsey-253161/)

    Video Review:
    Thank you BaRKy for reviewing my mod! I am honored! (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EWudgTJksMU)
  </description>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
        <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
        <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
        <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
        <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
</ModMetaData>
